artofflightmovie.com 2019-01-31

# Your Privacy Rights | Red Bull Policy Center

Updated and Effective on Jul 11, 2018  

### 1\. Introduction

1.1. This Red Bull Privacy Policy (" **Policy** ") sets out how Red Bull Media House North America, Inc. whose offices are at 1630 Stewart St., Santa Monica, CA 90404 (hereinafter “ **Red Bull** ”, " **we** ", " **us** ", " **our** ") collects and processes information about you when you, among other things, visit our website, use our applications on mobile phones or other consumer electronic devices, apply for a job, access our social media experiences or other experiences where this Policy is posted (the " **Properties** "). By continuing to use any of these Properties, you consent to your information being collected, processed and/or shared in accordance with this Policy.  

### 2\. Information we collect

2.1. We collect two types of “ **Information**.” Personally Identifiable Information and Non-Personally Identifiable Information. **Personally Identifiable Information** means any information that itself identifies you or would easily enable someone to contact and/or identify you, such as your name, social security number, email address or phone number. **Non-Personally Identifiable Information** refers to all other information about you that you may provide to us or that we may collect from you.  

2.2. You may actively give us Information, including Personally Identifiable Information, about yourself when you, among other things, use one of our Properties, create an account (" **Account** ") with us, subscribe to a newsletter, purchase a game, product or service, participate in a contest or sweepstakes, respond to a customer survey, email us, post in a public forum and/or use our chat/message functionality. The Personally Identifiable Information that you provide may include your name, gender, date of birth, email address, telephone number, delivery address, billing address and payment information, and login and password. Note also that Information you disclose in public chat and similar forums is accessible by anyone, including third parties not bound by this Policy.  

2.3. When you visit one of our Properties, we may also automatically collect, among other things, the following Information even if you have not actively given it to us: your IP address, log-in information, location information (for example, via GPS or WiFi), browser type and version, browser plug-in types and versions, operating system and platform, information about your visit including the URL clickstream to, through and from one of our Properties, products and/or content you viewed or searched for, download errors, length of visits to certain pages and page interaction, and in the case of our mobile applications, the other applications you have downloaded and how you use those applications. We collect Information automatically through the use of various technologies, including through "cookies", which is explained further below in Section 8.  

2.4. We acquire Information from other trusted sources (including, for example, business partners, advertising networks, search information providers, credit reference agencies and social media), and from other Red Bull entities and affiliates, to update or supplement the information you provided or we collected automatically. Note that this includes Information from your social media account when you grant us access to your social media account in connection with, for example, creating an Account with us. Where permitted by law, we may combine this information we receive from other sources, and with information you give to us or that we collect about you.  

2.5. If you have created an Account on one of our Properties, you may be able to obtain a copy of the Personally Identifiable Information we collect from you via your Account and correct, amend, or delete Personally Identifiable Information that is inaccurate. You may also close your Account altogether. Before we are able to respond to your request, we may ask you to verify your identity and to provide further details about your request. We will endeavour to respond within an appropriate timeframe and, in any event, within any timeframes required by law.  

2.6. It is your responsibility to ensure that you submit true, accurate and complete Information via your Account and keep it up to date. You may also update your Personally Identifiable Information by contacting us through the contact details provided below. Please make sure to include your name, username, and post code in your initial correspondence; this helps us protect the details and preferences on your Account from unauthorized access.  

2.7. If you are a California resident under the age of 18, and a registered user of any of our Properties, California law permits you to request and obtain removal of content or information you have publicly posted. To make such a request, please send us a detailed description of the specific content or information by clicking [here](http://energydrink-us.redbull.com/en/privacy-contact-form). Please be aware that such a request does not ensure complete removal of the content or information you have posted and that there may be circumstances in which the law does not require or allow removal even if requested.  

2.8. Notice to California Residents/Your California Privacy Rights: In addition, if you are a California resident California law also permits you to request a copy of the Personal Information we collect and third parties that received the Personal Information for the third parties' direct marketing purposes during the preceding calendar year. To make such a request, please send us a detailed description of the specific content or information by clicking [here](http://energydrink-us.redbull.com/en/privacy-contact-form).  

### 3\. How we use, share and disclose your information

3.1. We may use your Information for the purposes of enabling you to use our Properties, enabling us to fulfill orders you make (such as for products, services or newsletters), to send you marketing materials, and provide personalized content and experiences. We may also use the Information we collect automatically: (i) to administer our Properties for internal purposes, including troubleshooting purposes; (ii) optimize or improve our products, services, operations, and Properties; (iii) as part of our effort to keep our Properties safe and secure; (iv) to measure or understand the effectiveness of advertising we serve to you and others, and to deliver relevant advertising to you; (v) to communicate with you about your Account or transactions with us and send you information about features on our Properties or changes to our policies; (vi) to provide you with advertising based on your activity on our Properties and on third-party sites and applications; (vii) to make suggestions and recommendations to you and other users of our Properties about goods or services that may interest you or them; and (viii) to detect, investigate and prevent activities that may violate our policies or be illegal.  

3.2. We may share your Information with our Red Bull entities and affiliates and the third parties described in this Policy. We may also share your Information with third parties: (1) when we use a third party service provider to facilitate or offer our services; (2) when explicitly requested by you (e.g., with social media networks); (3) when required by a court order or any legal or regulatory requirement; (4) in connection with the sale or transfer of a business; (5) to enforce our Terms of Use; (6) to ensure the safety and security of our users, consumers and third parties; and (7) to protect our rights and property and the rights and property of our users and third parties. We may also share your Information with third parties for their direct marketing purposes where we think the third party offers products or services that may be of interest to you. See Section 4 for opt out rights if you do not want us to share your Personally Identifiable Information with third parties for third-party marketing purposes.  

### 4\. User choice, including how to opt in or opt out from direct marketing

4.1. As noted above, we and selected third parties with whom we share your Information, may use your Information for direct marketing purposes, including to provide updates, newsletters, events or other communications that we think may interest you. Where required by law, your prior consent will be obtained before we send direct marketing. In any event, we will offer you the option to unsubscribe from electronic marketing materials. And if you do not wish us to share your Personally Identifiable Information with third parties for their marketing purposes, please contact us by clicking [here](http://energydrink-us.redbull.com/en/privacy-contact-form).  

### 5\. Data Security and Retention

5.1. We apply appropriate security measures aimed at protecting your Personally Identifiable Information that is under our control from unauthorized access, collection, use, disclosure, copying, modification or disposal, but we can offer no guarantees or warranties related to such protection and are not responsible for such unauthorized activity. We will notify you in compliance with applicable law regarding any data breach. Where you have a password that enables you to access our Properties, you are responsible for keeping this password secure and confidential.  

5.2. Please be advised that we may retain some Information after you delete your Account, for example if necessary to meet our legal obligations or for tax and accounting purposes.  

### 6\. Links to other websites

6.1. Where we provide links to other websites or services, we do so for information purposes only. The other websites and services are outside our control and are not covered by this Policy. If you access other websites or services using the links provided, the operators of these websites and services may collect Information from you which will be used by them in accordance with their privacy policy, which may differ from ours. By accessing a third party website or link from our Properties, you hereby release us from any and all liability for your use of such website or link.  

6.2. On some pages of our Properties, third parties that provide content, services, applications or plug-ins through our Properties may directly track your use of content, applications and plug-ins or customize content, services, applications and plug-ins for you consistent with their privacy policies, which may differ from ours.  

### 7\. Use of Properties by minors

7.1. The features, programs, promotions and other aspects of our Services requiring the submission of personally identifiable information are not intended for children. We do not knowingly collect personally identifiable information from children under the age of 13. If you are a parent or guardian of a child under the age of 13 and believe he or she has disclosed personally identifiable information to us please [Contact Us](http://energydrink-us.redbull.com/en/privacy-contact-form). A parent or guardian of a child under the age of 13 may review and request deletion of such child's personally identifiable information as well as prohibit the use of that information.  

### 8\. Online Tracking - Cookies and other technologies

8.1. A “cookie” is a text file containing small amounts of information that a website can send to your browser, which may then be stored on your computer as a tag that distinguishes your computer but does not name you. Some of our Properties use cookies to better serve you when you return to the Property. You can set your browser to notify you before you receive a cookie, giving you the chance to decide whether to accept it. You can also set your browser to turn off cookies; however, if you do this, some of the features of our Properties may not work properly. You can also reject certain cookies served through Properties by opting out on the website of the third party placing the cookie, which you can identify through your browser.  

8.2. We may use or allow third parties to use tracking technologies (e.g., cookies, beacons, tracking pixels) to collect Non-Personally Identifiable Information about your browsing activities so that online advertisers can serve you advertising that better reflects your interests (“Interest-Based Ads”). For more information on Interest-Based Ads or to stop use of tracking technologies for these purposes, go to [www.aboutads.info](http://www.aboutads.info/) or [www.networkadvertising.org](http://www.networkadvertising.org/).  

8.3. We may also use local shared objects, sometimes known as “Flash cookies,” to store your preferences or display content based upon what you view on our site to personalize your visit. Our advertisers and third-party service providers also may use Flash cookies to collect and store information. Flash cookies are different from browser cookies because of the amount of, type of, and how data is stored. Cookie management tools provided by your browser will not remove Flash cookies. To learn how to manage privacy and storage settings for Flash cookies, please [click here](http://www.macromedia.com/support/documentation/en/flashplayer/help/settings_manager.html). If you disable Flash cookies, you will not have access to many features that make your guest experience more efficient and some of our services will not function properly.  

8.4. Finally, “Web beacons” are small pieces of data that are embedded in images on the pages of sites. Web beacons may involve the transmission of Information directly to us, to another party on our behalf, or to another party in accordance with its privacy policy. We may use Web beacons to bring together Information we collect about you.  

8.5. We may use third party tools to make the advertising we show you on our Properties and/or our partner websites more relevant and interesting to you. For this purpose, we use cookies, flash cookies, web beacons or similar technologies to collect information about your browsing behavior, and deliver interest-based ads to you.  

8.6. Certain browsers may offer you the option of providing notice to websites that you do not wish for your online activities to be tracked for preference based advertising purposes (“DNT Notice”). For a variety of reasons, we do not take any action based on browser based DNT Notices. Rather, if you do not wish to participate in preference based advertising activities, you should follow the simple opt-out processes identified above.  

### 9\. Changes to the Policy

9.1. A notice will be posted on our Properties for 30 days whenever this Policy is changed in a material way. By continuing to use our Properties you confirm your acceptance of the relevant changes.  

### 10\. Questions about this Policy

If you have a question, concern or complaint about this Policy or our handling of your information, you can contact us by [clicking here](http://energydrink-us.redbull.com/en/privacy-contact-form).
